# ABDELFATAH AHMED

## IT & INTERPRETER

## **PROFILE**

I am Abdelfatah Ahmed a 25 years old who has strong passion and interrest for Technology and interpreting. Being extremely neat, reliable, greatly motivated, able to deal with complicated projects, creating high quality and timely working results.

## **EDUCATION**

## **StArs Adult Education Program**

Advanced Class English 2016

## **Cairo University**

Faculty of Computers and Informations

## CONTACT

#### Phone:

01222775514

### **Email:**

abdelfatah.me@gmail.com

#### Web:

lebombastic.github.io

#### Home:

Hadayek-Elmaadi Egypt, Cairo

## **HIGHLIGHTS**

- Excellent problem solver
- Active listening skills
- Energetic work attitude
- Time management
- Confident

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Volunteer at StArs Youth Unaccompanied Program**

English Tutoring | Feb 2016 - June 2016

 Helping, Youth Refugees with english homework and making exercises to improve their speak, writing english.

## **Sio at St'Andrews Refugee Services**

Screening and Intake Officer | Sept 2016 - Dec 2016

• Responsible to screen refugee clients and refer them to the right program to receive the assistance they came for help either Financial, Education, Legal..

#### **Senior Sio at St'Andrews Refugee Services**

Senior Screening and Intake Officer | Jan 2017 - Present

- Responsible to screen refugee clients and refer them to the right program to receive the assistance they came for help either Financial, Education, Legal.
- Additional to Administrative Tasks.

## **SKILLS**

- English
- Arabic
- Somali
- Ms Office
- Coding

## **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- Attentive & Versatile
- Good
  Communication
- Multi-Tasking
- Loyalty

# **HOBBIES**

- Jogging
- Music

Reading